export const jsQuizz = {

    
        questions: [
          {
            question:
              "We all know kirby but, what is the name of the song?",
            choices: [
              "Float Islands",
              "Green Greens",
              "Bubbly Clouds",
              "Castle Lololo",
            ],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Float Islands",
            src:"src/audio/songs/04kirbyfloat.mp3",
            name:"Float Islands",
            composer:"Jun Ishikawa",
            arranger:"Xelerad",
            videogame:"Kirby's Dreamland"
          },
          {
            question:
              "To whom of the following Killer Instinct characters belongs this spooky tune?",
            choices: [
              "Spinal",
              "Orchid",
              "Sabrewulf",
              "Fulgore",
            ],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Sabrewulf",
            src:"src/audio/songs/03Sabrewulf.mp3",
            name:"Sabrewulf Theme",
            composer:"Robin Beanland",
            arranger:"Xelerad",
            videogame:"Killer Instinct"
          },
          {
            question: "Two fairies try to rescue their mother summonning ladders. Epic. ",
            choices: [
              "Rainbow Islands",
              "Rodland",
              "Pang",
              "A fairy Tale",
            ],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Rodland",
            src:"src/audio/songs/02Rodland.mp3",
            name:"Story 1- Track 1",
            composer:"Tsukasa Tawada",
            arranger:"Xelerad",
            videogame:"Rodland"
          },
          {
            question:
              "One of the most famous VG melodies. Shame on you if you fail",
            choices: ["Super Mario", "Tetris", "Pacman", "Sonic"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Sonic",
            src:"src/audio/songs/01Sonic.mp3",
            name:"Green Hills",
            composer:"Masato Nakamura",
            arranger:"Xelerad",
            videogame:"Sonic the Hedgehog"
          },
          {
            question: "It's a training robot named after an animal. Which one?",
            choices: ["Lobo", "Gato", "Perro", "Rana"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Gato",
            src:"src/audio/songs/05gato.mp3",
            name:"Gato Theme",
            composer:"Yasunori Mitsuda",
            arranger:"Xelerad",
            videogame:"Chrono Trigger"
          },
          {
            question: "One of the most addictive games of all time.",
            choices: [
                "Candy Crush Saga",
                "Angry Birds",
                "Fruit Ninja",
                "Flappy Bird",
            ],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Angry Birds",
            src:"src/audio/songs/12angry-birds-theme.mp3",
            name:"Main Theme",
            composer:"Ari Pulkkinen",
            arranger:"Raqanisu",
            videogame:"Angry Birds"
          },
          {
            question:
              "Ouch. Ay. Bungee. Booring. Die! Dont forget the wind direction.",
            
              choices: [
                "Worms",
                "Gran Turismo 2",
                "Command & Conquer",
                "Dungeon Keeper",
              ],
              type: "Song",
              correctAnswer: "Worms",
              src: "src/audio/songs/28worms-theme.mp3",
              name:"Worms Theme",
              composer:"Bjorn Lynne",
              arranger:"Raqanisu",
              videogame:"Worms"
              
          },
          {
            question: "It's a game about monkeys, that's for sure",
            choices: ["Monkey Island", "Tomba!", "Ape Scape", "Donkey Kong Country"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Donkey Kong Country",
            src:"src/audio/songs/06dkgalleon.mp3",
            name:"Gang-Plank Galleon",
            composer:"David Wise",
            arranger:"Xelerad",
            videogame:"Donkey Kong Country"
          },
          {
            question: "Street fighter character. 50% clich√© 50% WTF Japan",
            choices: ["Vega", "Honda", "Guille", "Dhalsim"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Vega",
            src:"src/audio/songs/07sf2vega.mp3",
            name:"Vega's Theme",
            composer:"Yoko Shimomura",
            arranger:"Xelerad",
            videogame:"Street Fighter"
          },
          {
            question: "IF you know how valve works, it's a 50% chance on this one.",
            choices: ["Portal", "Portal2", "Portal3", "Portal4"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Portal",
            src:"src/audio/songs/08portalstillalive.mp3",
            name:"Still Alive",
            composer:"Jonathan Coulton",
            arranger:"Xelerad",
            videogame:"Portal"
          },
          {
            question: "Song for the Card Game inside this Final Fantasy...",
            choices: ["Pazaak", "Tetra Master", "Gwent", "Triple Triad"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Triple Triad",
            src:"src/audio/songs/09ff8shuffleorboogie.mp3",
            name:"Shuffle or Boogie",
            composer:"Nobuo Uematsu",
            arranger:"Xelerad",
            videogame:"Final Fantasy VIII"
          },
          {
            question: "You can sing it but can you guess the town?",
            choices: ["Pallet Town", "Cerulean City", "Lavender Town", "Pewter City"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Pallet Town",
            src:"src/audio/songs/11pokemonpallettown.mp3",
            name:"Pallet Town",
            composer:"Junichi Masuda",
            arranger:"Xelerad",
            videogame:"Pokemon"
          },
          {
            question: "Main theme from this classic RPG",
            choices: ["Icewind Dale", "Baldur's Gate", "Diablo", "Planetscape Torment"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Baldur's Gate",
            src:"src/audio/songs/13baldurs-gate-theme.mp3",
            name:"Baldur's Gate Theme",
            composer:"Michael Honig",
            arranger:"Raqanisu",
            videogame:"Baldur's Gate"
          },
          {
            question: "Defeat the boss. Win the race. Super Mario 64 stage.",
            choices: ["Lethal Lava Land", "Dire Dire Docks", "Bob-omb Battlefield", "Birabuto Kingdom"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Bob-omb Battlefield",
            src:"src/audio/songs/14bobomb.mp3",
            name:"Bob-omb Battlefield",
            composer:"Koji Kondo",
            arranger:"Fisherman's Horizon",
            videogame:"Super Mario 64"
          },
          {
            question: "Chrono Trigger rickrolled us all with this song and we all liked it.",
            choices: ["Robo Theme", "Ayla Theme", "Frog Theme", "Magus Theme"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Robo Theme",
            src:"src/audio/songs/15chrono-trigger-robo-rickroll.mp3",
            name:"Robo Theme",
            composer:"Yasunori Mitsuda",
            arranger:"Raqanisu",
            videogame:"Chrono Trigger"
          },
          {
            question: "There's no way you can finish this game without savestates",
            choices: ["Contra", "Bad Dudes", "Broforce", "Metal Slug"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Contra",
            src:"src/audio/songs/16contra.mp3",
            name:"Jungle Theme",
            composer:"Kazuki Muraoka",
            arranger:"Fisherman's Horizon",
            videogame:"Contra"
          },
          {
            question: "This character was stupid AF but a pretty nice card",
            choices: ["Laguna", "Kiros", "Ward", "Wedge"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Laguna",
            src:"src/audio/songs/17ff-viii-the-man-with-the-machine-gun.mp3",
            name:"The Man with the Machine Gun",
            composer:"Nobuo Uematsu",
            arranger:"Raqanisu",
            videogame:"Final Fantasy VIII"
          },
          {
            question: "People from this village are not very friendly with Link",
            choices: ["Hyrule Field", "Goron City", "Kakariko Village", "Gerudo Valley"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Gerudo Valley",
            src:"src/audio/songs/19gerudo.mp3",
            name:"Gerudo Valley",
            composer:"Koji Kondo",
            arranger:"Fisherman's Horizon",
            videogame:"The Legend of Zelda"
          },
          {
            question: "Classic racing game",
            choices: ["F-Zero", "Mario Kart", "Diddy Kong Racing", "Gran Turismo"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "F-Zero",
            src:"src/audio/songs/18fzeroBigBlue.mp3",
            name:"Big Blue",
            composer:"Naoto Ishida",
            arranger:"Fisherman's Horizon",
            videogame:"F-Zero"
          },
          {
            question: "From a board game that belongs to the Warhammer universe ",
            choices: ["Heroquest", "Warhammer 40k", "Warhammer Fantasy", "Bloodbowl"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Heroquest",
            src:"src/audio/songs/20heroquest-theme.mp3",
            name:"Heroquest Theme",
            composer:"Neil Baldwin",
            arranger:"Raqanisu",
            videogame:"Heroquest"
          },
          {
            question: "Disney and Square TOGETHER in a videogme? That will suck. (Myself, a visionary)",
            choices: ["Destati", "Hikari", "Sanctuary", "Dearly Beloved"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Dearly Beloved",
            src:"src/audio/songs/21kingdom-hearts-dearly-beloved.mp3",
            name:"Dearly Beloved",
            composer:"Yoko Shimomura",
            arranger:"Raqanisu",
            videogame:"Kingdom Hearts"
          },
          {
            question: "Point. Click. Combine objects. Swear with style.",
            choices: ["Broken Sword", "Profesor Layton", "Monkey Island", "Day of the Tentacle"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Monkey Island",
            src:"src/audio/songs/22monkey-island-chapter-screen.mp3",
            name:"Dearly Beloved",
            composer:"Michael Land",
            arranger:"Raqanisu",
            videogame:"the Secret of Monkey Island"
          },
          {
            question: "Manage your troops in this futuristic? epic? or was it historic? world",
            choices: ["Age of Empires", "Starcraft", "Age of Mythology", "Warcraft 3"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Starcraft",
            src:"src/audio/songs/23starcraft-terran-theme.mp3",
            name:"Terran Theme",
            composer:"Glenn Stafford",
            arranger:"Raqanisu",
            videogame:"Starcraft"
          },
          {
            question: "Most famous melody from Monkey Island",
            choices: ["Chapter Screen", "The Scumm Bar","Intro", "leChuck's Theme"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Intro",
            src:"src/audio/songs/24monkey-island-theme.mp3",
            name:"Monkey Island Theme",
            composer:"Michael Land",
            arranger:"Raqanisu",
            videogame:"the Secret of Monkey Island"
          },
          {
            question: "Wait, this meme song comes from a videogame? NERD",
            choices: ["Ryu's Theme", "Ken's Theme", "Street Fighter's Theme", "Guile's Theme"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Guile's Theme",
            src:"src/audio/songs/25street-fighter-guille-theme.mp3",
            name:"Guile's Theme",
            composer:"Yoko Shimomura",
            arranger:"Raqanisu",
            videogame:"Street Fighter"
          },
          {
            question: "Business simulation game from the incredible Bullfrog",
            choices: ["Theme Park", "RollerCoaster Tycoon", "Theme Hospital", "Two Point Hospital"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Theme Hospital",
            src:"src/audio/songs/26theme-hospital-candy-floss.mp3",
            name:"Candyfloss",
            composer:"Russell Shaw",
            arranger:"Raqanisu",
            videogame:"Theme Hospital"
          },
          {
            question: "It's from the Warcraft series and named after the human race",
            choices: ["Warcraft", "Warcraft 2", "Warcraft 3", "World of Warcraft"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Warcraft 2",
            src:"src/audio/songs/27warcraft-2-human-theme.mp3",
            name:"Human Theme",
            composer:"Glenn Stafford",
            arranger:"Raqanisu",
            videogame:"Warcraft 2"
          },
          {
            question: "Quiet city from the Final Fantasy series",
            choices: ["Besaid", "Fisherman's Horizon", "Dali Village", "Costa del Sol"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Fisherman's Horizon",
            src:"src/audio/songs/29FishermansHOrizon.mp3",
            name:"Fisherman's Horizon",
            composer:"Nobuo Uematsu",
            arranger:"Raqanisu",
            videogame:"Final Fantasy VIII"
          },
          {
            question: "Boom. Tetris for Jonas.",
            choices: ["Tetris A", "Tetris B", "Tetris C", "Korobeiniki"],
            type: "Song",
            correctAnswer: "Tetris B",
            src:"src/audio/songs/10tetristypeb.mp3",
            name:"Tetris B",
            composer:"Hirokazu Tanaka",
            arranger:"Xelerad",
            videogame:"Tetris"
          },
        
        ],      
};

export const resultInitialState = {

    score:0,
    correctAnswers:0,
    wrongAnswers:0,

    
}

